Hello, my name is MPJ.
Hola, mi nombre es MPJ.
My full name is Mattias Petter Johansson.
Mi nombre completo es Mattias Petter Johansson.
But let's face it, you have as much chance on pronoucing that correctly as I have pronouncing "meal" in Portuguese.
Pero seamos sinceros, usted tiene tantas posibilidades de pronunciarlo correctamente do que you pronunciaré "comida" en portugués.
Efeiciauuuu (He tried to say "refeição")
Efeiciauuuu (Intentó hablar "comida")
I live in Sweden, wich is a country that is basically the opposite of Brazil: It's small, cold and introverted.
Yo vivo en Suecia, un país que es básicamente lo contrario de Brasil: Es pequeño, frío e introvertido.
Some of you might know me because during the weekends I produce an Youtube show, called "FunFunFunction".
Algunos de ustedes me conozcan, porque los fines de semana me producen un espectáculo en Youtube llamado "FunFunFunction".
During the week I work at Spotify, as a JavaScript developer on the desktop client,
Durante la semana trabajo en Spotify, como desarrollador de JavaScript en el desktop client,
wich is one of the most advanced JavaScript applications in the world.
que es una de las más avanzadas aplicaciones JavaScript en el mundo.
I'm very excited to be speaking at BrazilJS,
Estoy muy emocionado de ir apresentar una charla en BrazilJS,
because BrazilJS is the biggest JavaScript conference in the world.
porque BrazilJS es la mayor conferencia mundial de JavaScript.
And this is my biggest speaking engagement ever.
Y ese es mi mayor compromiso como speaker de todos los tiempos.
The audience is going to be huge!
El público va a ser enorme!
So, either you'll have the experience on watching an internet celebrity, as myself, die on the stage from a heart attack.
Así que, o tienes la experiencia de ver una celebridad de Internet, como yo, morir en el escenario de un ataque al corazón.
Or, I'll live through the talk, and you'll learn some very interesting things about functional programming in JavaScript.
O bien, voy a sobrevivir a la charla, y usted aprenderá muchas cosas interesantes acerca de la programación funcional con JavaScript.
I very much hope that you'll come to BrazilJS and see my talk.
Espero mucho que usted venga a BrazilJS y ves mi charla.
And should I survive, please grab me during the conference and have a chat about JavaScript.
Y si sobrevivo, por favor, me encontrará en la conferencia y hablaremos de JavaScript.
Come to BrazilJS!
Ven a BrazilJS!